Finding Aid for the Andrew West Photographs of the Guelaguetza, 1982-1985
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Color Slides
  - [Guelaguetza?]
    - Spectators, Performers, Close-ups, 1982 & 1985., 99 slides. (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Guelaguetza[?], man holding gourd, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], men holding gourd, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], men holding gourd, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], men holding gourd, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], necklaces close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], necklaces close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], necklaces close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], necklaces, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators [view from behind], 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators [view from behind], 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators [view from behind], 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators [view from behind], 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators [view from behind], 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators [view from behind], 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators [view from behind], 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators [view from behind], 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators [view from behind], 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], performers sitting with spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], woman dancer holding parasol close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Guelaguetza[?], women dancers close-up, 1982 or 1985
    - Miscellaneous - Duplicates, rejects, 1982 & 1985., 96 slides. (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Color Prints
  - Guelaguetza
    - San Sebastian Penoles - Oaxaca, 1985., Print 1 (8 × 10”). (Box 2)
    - Macuiltianquis - Sierra, 1985., Print 2 (8 × 10”). (Box 2)
  - Saints Day Celebration
    - Saints Day Celebration - Teotitlan de Valle, 1982., 1 print (8 × 10”). (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Sones de Pochutla - Region de la Costa, 1982., Print 3 (8 × 10”). (Box 2)
    - Musician signals beginning of festival, 1982., Print 4 (8 × 10”). (Box 2)
    - Musicians, 1985., Print 5 (8 × 10”). (Box 2)
    - Huatla de Jimenez - Canada, 1985., Print 6 (8 × 10”). (Box 2)
    - Tehuantepec - Istmo, 1985., Print 7 (8 × 10”). (Box 2)
    - Indian women watch the performance, as well as the dancers who have already performed, 1982., Print 8 (8 × 10”). (Box 2)
    - Betaza - Region de la Sierra, 1982., Print 9 (8 × 10”). (Box 2)
    - Ejutla de Crespo - Valle, 1985., Print 10 (8 × 10”). (Box 2)
    - San Antonio Castello de Verasco - Valle, 1985., Print 11 (11 × 14”). (Box 3)
    - Tlacolula, 1985., Print 12 (11 × 14”). (Box 3)
    - Tehuantepec - Istmo - Girls in gala dress and wearing partner's had during dance, 1982., Print 13 (11 × 14”). (Box 3)
    - Spectators, 1985., Print 14 (11 × 14”). (Box 3)
    - Ejutla de Crespo - Valle, 1985., Print 15 (11 × 14”). (Box 3)
    - Teotitlan - Valle, 1985., Print 16 (11 × 14”). (Box 3)
    - Mixistlan - Sierra, 1985., Print 17 (11 × 14”). (Box 3)
    - Macuiltianquis - Sierra, 1982., Print 18 (11 × 14”). (Box 3)
    - San Pedro Cajones - Sierra, 1985., Print 19 (11 × 14”). (Box 3)
    - Juchitan - Istmo, 1985., Print 20 (11 × 14”). (Box 3)
    - Calenda, 1982., Print 21 (16 × 20”). (Box 4)
    - Mixistlan - Sierra, 1985., Print 22 (16 × 20”). (Box 4)
    - Cotzocon - Sierra, 1985., Print 23 (16 × 20”). (Box 4)
    - Tlaxiaco - Mixteca - Region del Valle Janabe, 1982., Print 24 (16 × 20”). (Box 4)
    - Tuxtepec - Papaloapan, 1985., Print 25 (16 × 20”). (Box 4)
    - Tuxtepec - Papaloapan - Gift giving, 1985., Print 26 (16 × 20”). (Box 4)
    - Betaza - Sierra, 1985., Print 27 (16 × 20”). (Box 4)
    - Yalalag - Region de la Sierra, 1982., Print 28 (16 × 20”). (Box 4)
    - Lunes del Cerro - Setting, 1985., Print 29 (16 × 20”). (Box 4)
    - Ejutla de Crespo - Valle, 1985., Print 30 (16 × 20”). (Box 4)
- Documentation
  - Guelaguetza
    - Miscellaneous documentation, n.d., Documentation for color prints and slides. (Box 1, Folder 31)
- CD-R Disk
  - Guelaguetza
    - CD-R disk, n.d., Contains digital images of Guelaguetza. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Color images from CD-R disk, n.d., All images from CD-R disk (10pp.; 30 prints). (Box 1, Folder 33)